foreign
[Music]
[Applause]
I try
to
make you stay
but you're
Savage
[Applause]
[Music]
oh
thank you
wow big boys
[Music]
[Applause]
hey you
I'm just now leaving okay
[Music]
and you need time
less of course
that's fine
so go ahead and break my heart again
[Music]
are you the definition of insanity
over am I
oh it must be nice
to love someone oh you let you break
those wives
[Music]
[Applause]
it's okay later
that same perfume in those same size
go ahead and break my heart again
leave me wondering why the hell I ever
let you in
it must be like
to love someone
who lets you break once twice
[Music]
and you were here before
couldn't look here in the eyes
[Music]
it's just like an angel
your skin makes me cry
for all I can further
[Music]
forward
[Applause]
[Music]
what the hell am I doing here
[Applause]
[Music]
all right
she is
[Music]
what the hell am I doing here
I don't belong here
[Music]
I thought
[Applause]
oh
man close enough to start a war
all that I say you always say more
I can't keep up with the alternating
tables under your thumb I can't breathe
enough
[Music]
together
[Applause]
[Music]
all right
to turn on the tables
to turn the table
s
to turn in tables
[Music]
foreign
[Applause]
now
asking all my friends please
[Applause]
[Music]
but I wanna bridge too
foreign
[Applause]
[Music]
don't you please
see tell me
[Music]
[Applause]
the life
foreign
[Music]
[Applause]
To Make You Feel My Love
when the evening Shadows
there was no one there to dry your tears
I could hold you for a million years
To Make You Feel My Love
[Music]
you're wrong
I know it from the moment
[Applause]
where you belong
oh yeah
I couldn't make you happy make your
dreams come true
[Music]
there's nothing that I would not do
go to the air
yes of this Earth for you
To Make You Feel My Love
[Applause]
thank you
to make you feel
my
love
[Music]
[Applause]
jealous I'm over his eyes
when I'm down I get real down when I'm
high don't come down then I get angry
baby believe me
I can love you just like that and I can
leave it just as fast
[Music]
[Applause]
in the glory
[Music]
see I got issues
and one of them is
[Music]
sues
you
got it
so
I got it issues
[Applause]
[Music]
next to you
soon
[Music]
[Applause]
prison life
[Music]
[Applause]
thanks
party girls don't get hurt can't feel
anything when will I learn push it down
push it down
one two three one two three drink one
two three one two three
one two three one two three
all about the chorus
[Applause]
[Music]
foreign
[Applause]
[Music]
this is
what you get when you play with fire
[Music]
to my house
oh wow
it's so across
[Music]
this is what you get when you play with
fire
[Music]
[Applause]
and they're both
[Music]
[Applause]
if I can imagine
[Music]
[Applause]
oh
[Music]
[Applause]
oh
the king
[Applause]
[Music]
there were nights when the wind
when my body
[Music]
[Applause]
I finished crying in the international
[Music]
[Applause]
it's so hard to believe that it's all
coming back to me
It's All Coming Back It's All Coming
Back to Me Now
never know
ing
[Applause]
[Music]
baby
thank you
[Applause]
[Music]
I'm jealous of the rain
that falls upon your skin
it's closer than my hands have been
I'm jealous of the rain
foreign
[Music]
[Applause]
all I do is cry behind the smile I wish
you
the best ever
[Music]
heartbreaking misery
it's hard for me to say I'm jealous
[Music]
somebody said you got a new friend
[Applause]
[Music]
yeah I know it's stupid but I just gotta
see it for myself
oh
and I'm right over here why can't you
see me
[Applause]
[Music]
but I'm not the guy you're taking home
I'll keep Dancing On My Own
[Applause]
[Music]
mind
[Applause]
all four chairs that's huge
I'm in my bed
and shall not hear
you
and I can't take it back I can't unpack
the baggage
[Music]
and I'm Falling Again
[Applause]
[Music]
thank you
what am I now
what am I now what if yours
[Music]
[Applause]
yes
[Music]
met a strange lady
she made me nervous wow she took me and
she gave me breakfast beautiful wow
[Music]
[Applause]
I love his voice
[Music]
wake up
this is mine
[Music]
[Applause]
slack Jordan but not much to say
and I said to the man he tries
[Music]
[Applause]
ah
we mean glowing men plundered
[Music]
to cover
oh
[Music]
no one could save me
[Applause]
[Music]
in my life
[Applause]
[Music]
with you
never found that way
[Music]
[Applause]
fall in love
[Music]
[Applause]
the lights go down the show begins
[Music]
there's always tomorrow
I know
[Applause]
[Music]
tonight
[Applause]
[Music]
I miss you
oh so long
for this
[Laughter]
[Applause]
[Music]
to share with
me the special day
foreign
[Music]
[Applause]
go back and asleep
maybe once again
so that you
[Music]
will understand
[Applause]
[Music]
the sky
[Applause]
there's
[Music]
for love
[Applause]
restlessness alone
[Music]
right
and trenches up and arms
righteousness alone
[Music]
that I found of now or we've moved to
the coast as well and apparently I'm
looking more like you every day my
hair's gone curly like yours maybe even
more and I'm surfing away give you wave
I pause and I think of the way you're
engraved in the soul to the ocean the
place
[Applause]
[Music]
you wanna move
past your body scars the time just
and trenches
we find what we've been through
I'm done
[Applause]
[Music]
foreign
[Applause]
[Music]
whoa
quite as often as I could have
the little things I should have sitting
down
[Music]
I just never took that
but you always on my mind
[Applause]
[Music]
tell me
thousand times
[Music]
[Applause]
videos
[Music]
foreign
[Applause]
[Music]
oh my God
[Applause]
what is going on here
thank you
[Music]
[Applause]
foreign
[Music]
[Applause]
tell me
the way that you love me
from your point of view whoa yeah I
couldn't believe it or I see it for
myself
[Music]
it's all right
do that
is
[Music]
[Applause]
thank you I try to talk to my opinions
[Music]
[Applause]
cause no one hears me anymore
a hundred million stories and a hundred
million songs that feel stupid when I
sing
nobody's listening to me
nobody's listening
I talk to shooting stars but they always
getting wrong I feel stupid when I pray
don't
anyway
if nobody's needs anyone
please
[Music]
I need anyone
nobody's
live
[Applause]
listening
[Music]
foreign
[Applause]
[Music]
there's nothing I wouldn't do to have
just one more chance to look into your
eyes
[Music]
[Applause]
away
[Music]
end of her
help by hurting
you
[Music]
[Applause]
know
we may never meet again
before
we go
[Music]
[Applause]
we won't say
goodbye
[Applause]
[Music]
hold down my hands
and my heart will begin
for wrongly
nothing tonight
[Applause]
[Music]
no
[Applause]
[Music]
cotton days counting days since my level
been Gonna Stop Me
every breath that I've been taking since
[Music]
I've been holding on to all that you
come back when you can find some peace
[Music]
cause every word that I've been spoken
since your life is like a whole old
Street
[Music]
cold I've been told to get you off my
mind cause I hope I never lose the
bruises that you left behind oh my Lord
oh my Lord I need you by my side
there must be something in the water
us every day is getting colder
and if only I can order you
keep my head from going on
[Music]
even though I'm nothing till you're now
there must be something in the water
cause every day is getting cold
it was
[Music]
[Applause]
excuse me
[Music]
I've excused you for a while while I'm
white and I'm so damn good in the middle
in the night
[Music]
[Applause]
in the future
[Music]
wow amazing fun
dance
[Music]
thank you
baby
[Music]
yeah yeah
[Applause]
[Music]
trying hard to capture the moment this
morning I don't know
[Music]
as I dream about movies
a wake up French kiss a morning
[Music]
things
all right
[Music]
[Applause]
for anything
yeah
[Music]
[Applause]
I Wanna
Live down
[Music]
foreign
[Applause]
[Music]
foreign
no I'll be there
you will never be alone
[Music]
tonight
all I need is
[Music]
being still alive
[Applause]
[Music]
Is Your Love
to you
[Applause]
what's up
[Music]